One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, obtained everything the world has to offer.
What he said in his final moments drove countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
Go ahead.
Find it!
Everything is right where I left it!
People set their sights on the Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams.
The world has truly entered the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for
One Piece!
Compasses? Not for me. Left them all behind
I'm headed out to sea, with my heart serving as guide
Following the ancient map to the spot marked "X" reveals
Yeah, it's only legendary till someone proves it's real
When the world's got you down,
lean on your crew, they'll turn it around
Their biorhythm will carry you through
We're gonna make the most of it
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for
Got some change to my name,
and maybe you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are on the cruise!
WE ARE!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
Retreat for now, men!
Everyone! Find any way out you can!
– Wait for us!
Did we all make it?!
Are the people you were with
when you got off the ship here?!
Yes!
Yeah.
Yes.
Yep!
Captain Buggy isn't...
Captain Buggy isn't here!
Present Day
An Island in the East Blue
Alright!
I've finally finished my flashy raft!
Go!
Set sail!
Captain Buggy
(Missing a Few Parts)
What's with this crap so soon?!
The Adventures of Buggy's Crew
I refuse to lose! Damn you!
I'm gonna eat you!
Part-Part Cannon!
Quit struggling!
Just accept your fate!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
A Big Bird
Forgive me!
C'mon! C'mon!
My plan is foolproof!
Dummy! Dummy! Dummy!
I caught him!
I'm caught?! Huh?! What?!
How did things turn out this way?!
Stop! Stop! Ow, ow, ow!
Is the end here already?!
Stop–
Where am I now?
Leave this place!
Who's there?!
Begone from this island at once
if you value your life!
What are these things?
The animals of this forest.
Don't mess with them
unless you want to die!
Oh?
These animals are
pretty flashy and interesting...
I told you not to go any farther!
Blast it!
He snuck a shot at me!
Damn! I missed!
There you are!
What is this?!
Gotcha!
Come out!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Dammit! You have a devil fruit ability!
So what if I do?!
You're nothing...
You're...
What are you?
Did your family
treasure you too much?
Yes. Ever since I was a child,
they'd express their love for me by...
As if!
That joke got old fast!
Damn you! Don't get cocky!
I don't show mercy to anyone
who messes with these animals!
Oh? You wanna fight me?
I commend your bravery, but don't
go crying to me when you die!
Gotcha!
Blast you!
Ranged weapons are cheating!
Then what about this thing here?!
Stop being selfish!
Say your prayers!
Part-Part Quick Escape!
Ow!
How dare you?! Blast it! Ow!
How dare I what?! Huh?!
Anyone who messes
with the animals has to pay!
You came to this island
to go after these creatures!
Why would I do that?!
I didn't even want to come here!
You mean you're not a poacher?
What do you think? Good, huh?!
It's my very own cloudy sake!
Yeah, this is the best!
I can't remember
the last time I had a drink…
You can have as many refills
as you want! Drink up!
And I'm really sorry about earlier!
That was some horrible stuff you did,
but it's water under the bridge!
– Cheers!
Sorry for asking you
to help make a raft, too.
Not at all. It was my pleasure.
Okay! Take care of yourself!
You too!
Farewell, friend!
Take care!
Yeah...
You too!
Set sail!
Alright!
Buggy...
There are many strange
things in these waters.
Stay extra safe on your journey!
Wait, I forgot to tell him about that!
Get a move on, Buggy!
Look out!
Go! Get out of there!
What's that?
A Mysterious Woman
Pretty...
Who's that?
What a babe!
Well, at least he seems to be saved!
He had me sweating bullets there!
But anyway, take care of yourself!
Thanks for the help!
I flashily thought I was a goner there!
There's no need for thanks.
You're Buggy the Clown, right?
H-How do you know that?!
Who are you?
I'm looking for a certain man.
I believe you're acquainted?
That damn rubber brat!
Curse you!
Someday, I'll settle
the score with you!
Just you wait!
This is the guy you're looking for?
I see.
So that's why you helped me.
Well, what do you say?
Will you team up with me?
Sure, why not?
We both have the same goal.
Let's play ball.
That's great. Then cheers!
Cheers!
Captain Buggy!
When he was alive, I often felt
he was a ruthless and scary captain,
but now I realize he was a bold,
open-hearted, pirate's pirate!
Looking back, we were allowed
to pillage to our hearts' content
only because we had
Captain Buggy's support!
Today, let's hold the greatest,
flashiest funeral for Captain Buggy!
Captain, rest in peace!
Please leave everything to me,
Cabaji the Acrobat,
first officer of the Buggy Pirates!
I promise to rebuild the Buggy Pirates!
Hold it!
Cabaji!
What?!
It's only natural for Captain Buggy's
successor to be me,
the first mate and amazing
Beast Tamer Mohji!
I'm the captain!
Hey, guys!
We're gonna test our strength
to see who will be captain!
Fine by me!
– Mohji! Mohji! Mohji!
"Beast Tamer" Mohji
First Mate of the Buggy Pirates
– Cabaji! Cabaji! Cabaji!
Cabaji "the Acrobat"
First Officer of the Buggy Pirates
– Mohji! Mohji!
– Cabaji! Cabaji!
Looks like I'll just have to fight you
until your body falls apart!
Yeah, let's duke it out mano a mano.
I'll take you down with my bare hands!
Twelve Hours
Since the Battle Started
Damn you... J-Just give up already.
N-No, you give up already.
– Yes! Our Captain Richie!
– Captain Richie! Captain Richie!
– Our great captain!
With Captain Buggy now gone,
– Captain Richie! Captain Richie!
the most worthy of us
to be captain is Captain Richie!
– Our great captain!
– Captain Richie! Captain Richie!
Richie
Captain of the Richie Pirates
– Our great captain!
– Captain Richie! Captain Richie!
You do realize this island belongs
to us, the Bear Paw Tribe, right?!
Captain!
How amusing.
Are you picking a fight?!
W-We surrender.
Did you find something good?
Yeah! That's...
the Buggy Pirates'
super flashy pirate ship!
But who did this? What bad luck!
Not to mention this is
an old wanted poster.
Oh? There's someone
on the ground there.
Wha...?!
Mohji! Cabaji!
What happened to you guys?!
C-Captain Buggy...
I-It's so good to see you.
I'm so glad you're alive!
I thought we'd never see you again!
I-I'm so happy, too!
But what the hell happened here?
Who did this to you?!
Huh?
We were punched out of the blue.
It's embarrassing, but we
can't remember a thing.
The Bear Paw Tribe did this.
If you're going to save them,
you'd better hurry.
Bear Paw tribesmen are famous
for their discerning palates.
The captain says that lions taste bad!
We taste bad too!
I won't make a good meal at all!
This guy looks better to eat than me!
Lies! Lies!
He tastes much better!
I'm all bones! There's
hardly any meat on me!
Don't worry!
We're the Bear Paw Tribe!
That makes us iron chefs!
Some wine and spices
will take your smell away!
What do we do with this food?
What are they?
I've never seen such
odd ingredients.
Do we boil this with them?
I just hope it doesn't
upset my stomach.
Part-Part-Part...
Part-Part-Part-Part...
Is that...?!
...Flashily Reassemble!
I'm back!
Buggy "the Clown"
Captain of the Buggy Pirates
– Captain Buggy!
Sorry I took so long, men!
Time to liven things up
with a super flashy Buggy Ball!
Richie!
Acrobatics: Steamy Hot Spring
Murder Mystery!
Let the beast-taming show begin!
Do you really think you can hit me,
the great Buggy the Clown?!
I have to thank you all
for everything you did to my men!
Here I flashily come!
Part-Part Kick!
Part-Part Punch!
That's our captain!
– Captain Buggy!
I'm so glad you're safe!
I've caused you all such pain,
my dear underlings!
Our pain is nothing at all!
All the hardships you've had
were because of...
that damn Straw Hat!
By the way, who is
this lovely, young lady?
This nice woman saved
my life! Her name is...
Uh...
Um, I'm sorry.
What was your name again?
Everyone!
The Buggy Pirates are back in action!
Captain! What should we do first?
Get the head of Monkey D. Luffy!
More feelings than I can hold but I can’t make you understand
Be that as it may, I just can’t bear to let go of your hand
I’ve still gotta move, even if I’m alone I’ll walk along
Just promise that you’ll still keep an eye on me when I am gone
As soon as I woke up, couldn’t get it off my mind
“Why the hell’s it so hot? I can hardly breathe!”
It’s been quite a while, but those thoughts just won’t seem to let go
But hey, what do I know?
Guess I want a taste of that thing people call a “runner’s high”
Think I chased too hard, and ended up leaving myself behind
All I want’s a taste of a dream that a sentence can’t define
Stick right by my side, and I can run, run, run until I die